flysn.com 2013-10-08

# Brussels Airlines - Security & privacy policy

Home > Misc >  **Security & privacy policy**

According to the provisions of the Belgian Act of 8 December 1992 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, we provide you with the following information.

##  **Personal data**  

Your personally identifiable data are processed by Brussels Airlines nv, with registered office at 1050 Brussels (Belgium), Jaargetijdenlaan 100-102 B30, in its capacity of Controller of the personal data. 

The processing of your data is performed to provide you with the services for which you have registered with us (e.g. to receive news updates on Brussels Airlines products and services via e-mail, to process your requests for information and/or comments on our products and services, and for the processing and confirmation of web bookings.

In addition to information connected with services for which you have subscribed, we may contact you with other information and about other products and services of Brussels Airlines which may be of interest to you, and with information about ‘Miles & More’, the frequent flyer programme of Brussels Airlines.

Brussels Airlines will use personal data only for the purposes indicated above.

Subject to the above and except to the extent that communications of personal data to companies whose intervention   as data processors, acting on behalf and under the sole control of Brussels Airlines, is required to accomplish the purposes indicated above, Brussels Airlines will not disclose, sell, rent or exchange such personal data to any other organization or entity, unless you are first notified and expressly agreed with it, or as otherwise required by law.

We draw your attention to the fact that you have the right to access and restrict your data and, where appropriate, request rectification of any erroneous data relating to you. You may furthermore, at any moment, object by means of a simple request and free of charge, to the future processing of personal data relating to you for the purpose of direct marketing. These rights may be exercised by sending an e-mail regarding any questions you may have to [info@brusselsairlines.com](mailto:info@brusselsairlines.com) or by post at the aforesaid address.

Our Website contains links to other websites not owned or operated by Brussels Airlines. Please be aware that Brussels Airlines is not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites and that this Privacy Policy applies solely to data collected by our Website.

##  **Cookies and action tags**  

We also collect non-personally identifiable information passively using “cookies” and “action tags”. 

"Cookies" are small text files that are placed on your computer in order to identify your web browser and the activities of your computer on our website and other websites. We may use Cookies to allow us to statistically monitor how you are using our website to help us improve our online offerings, or to determine the popularity of certain content. Although most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, you may reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally. Most browsers offer instructions on how to do so in the "Help" section of the toolbar. While you are not required to accept our cookies to access our Website, if you reject cookies, certain offerings, features, or resources of our Website may not work properly and you may experience some loss of convenience. 

"Action tags," also known as web beacons or gif tags, are a web technology used to help track website usage information, such as how many times a specific page has been viewed.   Action tags are invisible to you, and any portion of our Website, including advertisements, or email sent on our behalf, may contain action tags.   We may select and use from time to time different third parties to track website usage through action tags on our Website. 

By using cookies and action tags together, we are able to gain valuable information to improve our Website and our online offerings and measure the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing campaigns.  

Finally, please note that advertisers and other third parties may also use their own cookies or action tags when you click on their advertisement or link to their website or service, on or from our Website.  

This Privacy Policy does not govern the use of cookies or action tags by such third-party websites or providers of third-party advertising. 

##  **Security**  

To ensure secure online payment and security where personal data is involved, the Website uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer ) technology.

A secure connection is shown by a closed lock in the bottom left (Netscape) or right (Internet Explorer) corner of your browser window. For further information, please consult your browser’s security specifications.

If your browser is equipped with SSL (i.e. Netscape 2.0 and higher or Internet Explorer 3.0 and higher), your transaction will automatically be secured.
